griffith.ie 2017-12-14

# Privacy & Legal | Griffith College

The information contained on this website is intended as a guide for persons seeking admission to Griffith College, and shall not be deemed to constitute a contract or the terms thereof between the College and a student or any third party. The College reserves the right to cancel, suspend or modify in any way the contents of this website.  
Griffith College reserves the right to change any of the details and validation bodies listed for any course. Course commencement is dependent on student demand.

This is a statement of the practices of Griffith College (the "College") in connection with the capture of personal data on this website (that is all web pages within the domain www.griffith.ie and the steps taken by the College to respect your privacy). The College is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites which may be accessed through the Griffith College website. It is College policy to identify clearly links to external websites and it is your responsibility to satisfy yourself as to the adequacy of the practices of linked sites. The College's policy regarding the use of College web resources may be inspected at www.griffith.ie.

The College fully respects your right to privacy and actively seeks to preserve the privacy rights of those who share information with the College. The College will not collect any personal information about you on this website without your permission, except as may be required or permitted by law. Any personal information which you volunteer to the College will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, in accordance with the Data Protection Acts, 1988 and 2003.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

Any information which you provide in this way is not made available to any third parties, and is used by the College only in accordance with the purpose for which you provided the information and will only be retained for as long as required for the purpose. This is normally stated on the webpage where the information is requested and should be self-explanatory. However, if you have any specific queries about the purpose for which your information is to be used, you should contact our Information Compliance Officer before submitting the information.

The College uses HubSpot as its inbound marketing platform. This enables us to more effectively deal with applications and enquiries by providing more relevant information, and thus a better service to potential applicants. HubSpot data is held outside of the EU. The College has a model clauses agreement in place with HubSpot which ensures data is managed in a way that adheres to EU data protection requirements. Further information can be found on the [_Cookie Policy_](https://www.griffith.ie/cookiepolicydocument) page on our website.

We also partner with Xtremepush to collect names and email addresses from incomplete applications and enquiries. This information is used for the sole purpose of providing technical support and followup information and will not be used for marketing purposes. Further information can be found in the[ Xtremepush Privacy Policy.](https://xtremepush.com/cookies-policy/)

## Collection and Use of Technical Information

Information on internet traffic is collected routinely by the College and also at other points along the route in the internet (e.g. HEAnet). This technical information is used to ensure the smooth running of the computer network in the College and for statistical or administrative purposes. It is NOT used to gather identifiable personal information on individual website visitors, except in so far as this is permitted by law and may be necessary in order to prevent or detect problems or offences in relation to the operation of the website.

Pursuant to the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003, you have certain rights to obtain a copy of the data held about you, for a fee. Any such requests should be made in writing (not email) to the Information Compliance Officer at the address set out below. For further details on your data privacy rights, please refer to [www.dataprotection.ie](http://www.dataprotection.ie/).

This statement should not be construed as a contractual undertaking. The College reserves the right to review and amend this statement at any time without notice and you should therefore re-visit this webpage from time to time.

Any queries or concerns you may have about the processing of personal information on this website should be addressed to: The Quality Assurance Officer, South Circular Road, Dublin 8, Ireland Email: info@gcd.ie Telephone: +353 1 4150400
